A Guide to the National Association of Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Counselors, 1970-2000
Library of Virginia
- NAADAC General Historical - History (Box 62-62A)
  - NAACT Articles of Incorporation and Charter from the state of California-1974 (also includes correspondence pertaining thereto) (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Charters for NAACT and NAAC from the Commonwealth of Virginia-1975-1976 (includes Articles of Incorporation for NAAC-1976) (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - NAACT-National conference-Denver, CO-July 1975 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Name change from NAAC to NAADAC-1980-1982 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - NAADAC Articles of Incorporation 1982 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - By-laws/elections (minutes pertaining thereto) (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - By-laws and revisions-1979-1989 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - By-laws-Drafts and revisions-1982 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - By-laws changes committee-1981-1982 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - By-laws committee-1982 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Policy and position papers (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Policies and procedures manual-adopted 8 July 1989 and revised 18 October 1989, 27 June 1991, 11 September 1991, 5 February 1992 (Box 62A, Folder 1)
- NAADAC General Historical - Board Mailings (Box 62A)
  - Board minutes and related materials (Box 62A, Folder 2-5)
  - Board mailings--VADACA;; ICAADA planning for NAADAC '84; resignation; U. S. Journal articles (Box 62A, Folder 6)
- NAADAC General Historical - Correspondence (Box 62A-63)
  - George Anderson correspondence (Box 62A, Folder 7)
  - LeClair Bissil correspondence (Box 62A, Folder 8)
  - Bill Callahan correspondence (Box 62A, Folder 9)
  - Robert T. Dorris correspondence (Box 62A, Folder 10)
  - Jan Gomien--IACCB--correspondence (Box 62A, Folder 11)
  - Terry Gorski correspondence and related material (Box 62A, Folder 12)
  - Linda Grant correspondence and related material (Box 62A, Folder 13)
  - Harold Hughes--eulogy (Box 62A, Folder 14)
  - Kay Johnson--word processing (Box 62A, Folder 15)
  - Lynn Kronzek correspondence (Box 62A, Folder 16)
  - Ernie Kurtz correspondence (Box 62A, Folder 17)
  - Tom Lief correspondence (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - David Lombard correspondence (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Paul Lubben--report and photograph (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Robert G. Niven--NIAAA--correspondence (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Lydia H. Norie correspondence and related material (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Don Osborne correspondence (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - David W. Oughton correspondence and related material (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Roy Preston--report (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Greg Raduka correspondence (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Matt Rose correspondence (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Mel Schulstad correspondence (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Joan Shellene correspondence (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - G. Douglas Talbott, M.D. correspondence (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Steve K. Valle correspondence and related material (Box 63, Folder 14-15)
  - Computer consultant (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (Box 63, Folder 17)
- NAADAC General Historical - Organizations (Box 63-64)
  - Council of Alcoholism/Addiction Professionals 1976 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Coalition for the Prevention of Alcohol Problems (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Department of Transportation (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - NAAC and NCAE/NCAE and NAAC (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - NAACT--Guidance memoranda 1975-1977 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - NAADAC News--State organizations (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - National Council on Alcohol (NCA) (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - NCC, NCAC (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - National Coalition for Adequate Alcoholism Program-1976 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - NIAAA Remembers: Milestones in the History of the Alcohol Field (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - NIAAA (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
  - NIDA/Relapse prevention (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Society of Americans for Recovery, Inc. (SOAR) (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - White House (Box 64, Folder 6)
- NAADAC General Historical - Conferences (Box 64-65)
  - National Conference--Lexington KY 1981 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - National Conference--Long Beach CA 1982 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - National Conference--Houston TX 1983 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - National Conference--Indianapolis IN 1984 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - National Conference--Atlanta GA 1985 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - National Conference--Las Vegas NV-1986 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - National Conference-New Orleans LA 1987 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - National Conference--Orlando FL 1988 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - National Conference--San Francisco CA-1989 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - National Conference--Boston MA 1990 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - National Conference--San Antonio TX 1991 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - National Conference--Washington DC-1992 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - National Conference--Chicago IL 1993 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - National Conference--San Diego CA 1994 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - National Conference--Orlando FL 1995 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - National Conference--Minneapolis MN 1996 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - National Conference--San Francisco CA-1997 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - National Conference-San Francisco CA-1997 (slide presentation-script and negatives) (see also box 68 for slides); National Conference-Chicago IL-1998 (conference papers); National Conference-Denver CO-2000 (conference papers) (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - National Conference-Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 10)
- NAADAC General Historical - Annual Board of Directors Meetings (see also boxes 79-83) (Box 65A-66)
  - 1976-Annual Meeting-Atlanta GA (NAAC) (Box 65A, Folder 1)
  - 1977-Annual Meeting-Kansas City KS (Box 65A, Folder 2)
  - 1978-Annual Meeting-Memphis TN (Box 65A, Folder 3)
  - 1979-Annual Meeting-Cincinnati OH (Box 65A, Folder 4)
  - 1980-Annual Meeting-Syracuse NY (Box 65A, Folder 5)
  - 1981-Annual Meeting-Lexington KY (Box 65A, Folder 6)
  - 1982-Annual Meeting-South Bend IN (Box 65A, Folder 7)
  - 1983-Annual Meeting-Houston TX (Box 65A, Folder 8)
  - 1984-Annual Meeting-Indianapolis IN (Box 65A, Folder 9)
  - 1985-Annual Meeting-Atlanta GA (Box 65A, Folder 10)
  - 1986-Annual Meeting-Las Vegas NV (Box 65A, Folder 11)
  - 1987-Annual Meeting-New Orleans LA (Box 65A, Folder 12)
  - 1988-Annual Meeting-Orlando FL (Box 65A, Folder 13)
  - 1989-Annual Meeting-San Francisco CA (Box 65A, Folder 14)
  - 1990-Annual Meeting-Boston MA (Box 65A, Folder 15)
  - 1991-Annual Meeting-San Antonio TX (Box 65B, Folder 1)
  - 1992-Annual Meeting-Washington DC (Box 65B, Folder 2-3)
  - 1993-Annual Meeting-Chicago IL (Box 65B, Folder 4)
  - 1994-Annual Meeting-San Diego CA (Box 65B, Folder 5)
  - 1995-Annual Meeting-Orlando FL (Box 65B, Folder 6)
  - 1996-Annual Meeting-Minneapolis MN (Box 65B, Folder 7)
  - 1998-Annual Meeting-Chicago IL (Box 65B, Folder 8-10)
  - (Folder 8 contains the 1997 financial statement for NAADAC, NERF, and NAADAC PAC)
  - Legislative Conferences (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Regional Conferences (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Colorado meeting (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Counselors Networking Reception-WAADAC (Box 66, Folder 4)
- NAADAC General Historical - Education--Seminars, Workshops, Training (Box 66-66A)
  - Assessment and Treatment of Adolescents and Young Adults-3-5 November 1986 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Peer Assistance in the Counseling Profession-29-31 March 1987 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Ethics--October 1988 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Introductory and Advanced Workshops on Clinical Supervision-1989 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Advanced Clinical Supervision Workshops-1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Dual Disorders--September-October 1991; March 1992; May 1996 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Rational Recovery-5 June 1992 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Relapse--September-October 1992; September 1993 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Treatment in the Criminal Justice System-22-23 March 1993 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Group Therapy--April 1993 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - The Criminal Offender--March, September 1994 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Heroin--April 1994 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Addiction Science--April-May 1994 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - ASAM Patient Placement Criteria--April-June 1994; April-May, September-October 1995 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - HIV/AIDS--October-November 1994; January, May, September 1995 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - DSM IV--September-October 1995 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Fall 1996 workshop (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Clinicals (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Directory of Education and Training (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Education schedule (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Gallup Organization Educational Study for NAADAC (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Self-Study for Substance Abuse Professional (SAP)-Procedures guidelines-Department of Transportation's regulations module (includes self exam) (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - NAADAC Education and training program evaluation-1990 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - How to Develop a Private Practice-for NAADAC Regional Conference on Addiction Treatment-20 March 1993 (Box 66A, Folder 1-2)
  - NERI (National Education and Research Institute) Training Seminars (Box 66A, Folder 3-4)
  - Technical Proposal for Substance Abuse Counselor Training--vol. I (Box 66A, Folder 5-6)
  - Appendices--Substance Abuse Counselor Training--vol. II (Box 66A, Folder 7-8)
- NAADAC General Historical - Journals, Newsletters (Box 67-68)
  - Advertising in The Counselor (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Mailing monitor (The Counselor) (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - The Counselor promotional material (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - U. S. Journal--Articles (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - U. S. Journal--other (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Subscription (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous newsletters and catalogs (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Advertising 1996 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Insurance (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Leadership Issue (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Membership (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Treatment Works! (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Counselors Delegation to Russia and the Czech Republic-1996 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - The Certified Alcohol and Other Drug Abuse Counselors in Health Care-6 June 1993-a joint report by NAADAC and ICRC/AODA (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 15-16)
  - Buttons, pins, stamps, seals, cards, lapel pins, flags, cassette tapes, VCR tapes, slides (Box 68)
- Board Mailings - Correspondence (Box 69-78)
  - 1976--Correspondence, proposals, agendas (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - 1977--Correspondence, agendas (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - 1978--Correspondence, surveys (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - 1979--Correspondence, memos, meeting agendas, budgets, resolutions (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - 1980--Correspondence, agendas, budgets, surveys, fact sheets, NAAC Updates (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - 1981--Correspondence, agendas, budgets, audit report (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - 1982--Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - 1983--Correspondence (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - 1984--Correspondence, by-laws change consent (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - 1985--Correspondence, related materials (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - 1986--Correspondence--January-August (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - 1986--Correspondence--September-December, n.d.; and miscellaneous (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - 1987--Correspondence--January-March (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - 1987--Correspondence--April-June (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - 1987--Correspondence--July-December, n.d.; miscellaneous (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - 1988--Correspondence (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - 1989--Correspondence--January-March (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - 1989--Correspondence--April-June (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - 1989--Correspondence--July-December (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - 1990--Correspondence--January-March (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - 1990--Correspondence--April (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - 1990--Correspondence--May (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - 1990--Correspondence--June (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - 1990--Correspondence--July (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - 1990--Correspondence--August (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - 1990--Correspondence--September-December (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - 1991--Correspondence--January (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - 1991--Correspondence--February (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - 1991--Correspondence--March (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - 1991--Correspondence--April (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - 1991--Correspondence--May (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - 1991--Correspondence--June (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - 1991--Correspondence--July (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - 1991--Correspondence--August (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - 1991--Correspondence--September (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - 1991--Correspondence--October (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - 1991--Correspondence--November (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - 1991--Correspondence--December, n.d (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - 1992--Correspondence--January-February (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - 1992--Correspondence--March (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - 1992--Correspondence--April-May (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - 1992--Correspondence--June (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - 1992--Correspondence--July (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - 1992--Mailings--22 July (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - 1992--Correspondence--August-September (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - 1992--Correspondence--October (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - 1992--Mailings--26 October (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - 1992--Correspondence--November (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - 1992--Correspondence--December (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - 1993--Correspondence--January (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - 1993--Correspondence--February (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - 1993--Correspondence--March (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - 1993--Mailings--March (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - 1993--Correspondence--April (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - 1993--Correspondence--May (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - 1993--Correspondence--June (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - 1993--Correspondence--July (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - 1993--Correspondence--August (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - 1993--Correspondence--September (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - 1993--Correspondence--October (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - 1993--Correspondence--November (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - 1993--Correspondence--December, n. d. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - 1994--Correspondence--January (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - 1994--Correspondence--February (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - 1994--Correspondence--March (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - 1994--Mailing--18 March (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - 1994--Correspondence--April (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - 1994--Mailing--20 April (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - 1994--Correspondence--May-June (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - 1994--Mailing--23 May (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - 1994--Correspondence--July-August (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - 1994--Mailing--2 August (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - 1994--Correspondence--September (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - 1994--Correspondence--October (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - 1994--Correspondence--November-December (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - 1995--Correspondence--January (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - 1995--Correspondence--February (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - 1995--Correspondence--1-19 March (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - 1995--Correspondence--20-31 March (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - 1995--Mailing--15 March (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - 1995--Correspondence--April (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - 1995--Mailing--19 April (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - 1995--Correspondence--1-19 May (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - 1995--Correspondence--20-31 May (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - 1995--Correspondence--June (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - 1995--Correspondence--July (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - 1995--Correspondence--August (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - 1995--Mailing--9 August (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - 1995--Correspondence--September (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - 1995--Mailing--14 September (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - 1995--Correspondence--October (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - 1995--Correspondence--November (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - 1995--Correspondence--December (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - 1996--Correspondence--January (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - 1996--Correspondence--February (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - 1996--Correspondence--March (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - 1996--Correspondence--April (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - 1996--Correspondence--May (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - 1996--Correspondence--June (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - 1996--Correspondence--July (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - 1996--Correspondence--August (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - 1996--Correspondence--September (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - 1996--Mailing--25 September (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - 1996--Correspondence--October (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - 1996--Mailing--30 October (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - 1996--Correspondence--November (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - 1996--Correspondence--December (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - 1997--Correspondence--January (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - 1997--Mailing--30 January (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - 1997--Correspondence--February (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - 1997--Correspondence--March (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - 1997--Mailing--13 March (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - 1997--Correspondence--April (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - 1997--Correspondence--May (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - 1997--Correspondence--June (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - 1997--Correspondence--July (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - 1997--Correspondence--August (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - 1997--Mailing--28 August (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - 1997--Correspondence--September (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - 1997--Mailing--26 September (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - 1997--Correspondence--October (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - 1997--Correspondence--November (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - 1997--Correspondence--December (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Annual Meeting (see also boxes 65A-65B) (Box 79-83)
  - 1984--Annual meeting--Indianapolis IN (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - 1985--Annual meeting--Atlanta GA--Minutes and related materials (Box 79, Folder 2-3)
  - 1986--Annual meeting--Las Vegas NV--Minutes, related material (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - 1986--Annual meeting--Las Vegas NV--Reports, correspondence, related material (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - 1987--Annual meeting--New Orleans LA--orientation, seating, minutes (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - 1987--Annual meeting--New Orleans LA--materials (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - 1988--Annual meeting--Orlando FL--index, agenda, opening statements (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - 1988--Annual meeting--Board minutes 1987-1988 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - 1988--Annual meeting--Orlando FL--financial (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - 1988--Annual meeting--reports, miscellaneous (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - 1988--Annual meeting--Orlando FL--minutes (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - 1989--Annual meeting--San Francisco CA--materials (Box 80, Folder 4-6)
  - 1989--Annual meeting--San Francisco CA--minutes (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - 1990--Annual meeting--Boston MA--materials (Box 80, Folder 8-9)
  - 1990--Annual meeting--Boston MA--materials (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - 1990--Annual meeting--Boston MA--minutes (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - 1991--Annual meeting--San Antonio TX--material (Box 81, Folder 3-4)
  - 1992--Annual meeting--Washington DC--material (Box 81, Folder 5-6)
  - 1992--Annual meeting--Washington DC--minutes, miscellaneous material (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - 1993--Annual Meeting--Chicago IL--material (Box 81, Folder 8-9)
  - 1994--Annual meeting--San Diego CA--July (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
  - 1996--Annual meeting--Minneapolis MN--July (Box 82, Folder 3-4)
  - 1997--Annual meeting--San Francisco CA--July (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - 1997--Annual meeting--San Francisco CA--July (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - 1997--Executive Committee material for July annual meeting--20 June (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Board Mailings - Executive Committee Meetings--Winter (Spring) (Box 83-85)
  - 1986--Executive Committee meeting--April--Washington DC (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - 1987--Executive Committee meeting--April--Washington DC (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - 1988--Executive Committee meeting--February--Washington DC (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - 1989--Executive Committee meeting--February--Washington DC (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - 1990--Executive Committee meeting--February (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - 1991--Legislative Conference--February (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - 1991--Executive Committee meeting--February (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - 1992--Executive Committee meeting--Washington DC--February (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - 1993--Executive Committee meeting--Washington DC--February (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - 1994--Executive Committee meeting--February-March (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - 1995-Executive Committee meeting--Washington DC-February (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - 1995-Executive Committee meeting-Washington DC-February (extra materials) (Box 84, Folder 5-6)
  - 1995-Executive Committee meeting-Washington DC-February (minutes) (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - 1996--Executive Committee meeting--Washington DC--March (Box 84A, Folder 1-2)
  - 1997--Executive Committee meeting--Washington DC--March (Box 85, Folder 1-2)
- Board Mailings - Executive Committee Meetings--Fall (Box 85-86)
  - 1990--Executive Committee meeting--September (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - 1990--Executive Committee meeting--October (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - 1992--Executive Committee meeting--Hilton Head SC--September (Box 85, Folder 5-6)
  - 1993--Executive Committee planning meeting--October (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - 1994--Material for Fall planning notebook--September (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - 1994--Executive Committee Fall planning--September (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - 1995--Executive Board meeting--September (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - 1996--Executive Committee Fall planning meeting--October (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Board Mailings - Board and Committee Meetings, Materials (Box 86)
  - 1983--Agendas, board minutes, miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - 1984--Board meeting minutes (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - 1986--Board minutes--teleconferences (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - 1987--Board minutes--teleconferences (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - 1990--National Credential Informational Meeting--July (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - 1991--Executive Committee conference call and related material--April (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - 1993--Materials for 4 May conference call--22 April (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - 1997--Executive Committee teleconference--9 February (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - 1997--Executive Committee teleconference mailing--1 May (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Board Mailings - Committees (Box 87)
  - 1994--1994-1996 Committee chairmen (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - 1995--Tactics Committee-February (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Board Mailings - By-laws, Reports, Manuals, Papers (Box 87)
  - 1982--Draft of NAADAC By-laws (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - 1986--By-laws, committees, miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - 1995--By-laws (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - 1996--Selected Position Statements 1986-1996 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - 1993--Policies and Procedures (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - 1996--President's and Committee Reports (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - 1997--NAADAC focus groups and report--8 February (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Board Mailings - Financial (Box 87)
  - 1989--Financial and miscellaneous (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - 1995--Finances and leadership--July (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - 1996--Financial statement--March (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Board Mailings - Membership (Box 87)
  - 1990--Membership report and survey--January (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - 1993--Membership campaign (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - 1993--Membership correspondence and development (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - 1995--New membership (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Board Mailings - Miscellaneous (Box 88)
  - 1982--Reports, agendas, agreements, miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - 1983--Logo designs (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - 1990--Health and Welfare Canada--February (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - 1990--NCAADACCB by-laws (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - 1991--New Hampshire copyright issue (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - 1991--Resolution vote--August (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - 1993--Health Care Reform (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - 1995--CSAT conference grant (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - 1995--Peer Assistance Manual (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - 1996--Articles--August (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - 1996--Cynthia J. Moreno's Travel Log 1994-1996 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Correspondence/Miscellaneous - Correspondence (Box 89-93)
  - 1979--Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - 1980--Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - 1982--Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - 1982-1983--David G. Evans--Confidentiality (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - 1982-1983--Paul F. Murgo (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - 1982-1986--Tom Clauch (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - 1983--Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - 1983--Doris Gray (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - 1983--Amos M. Long (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - 1983--Susan McGrath (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - 1983--Dennis Miller-Conferencecorder (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - 1983--Bill Swegan (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - 1983--Jack Way (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - 1983--David A. Wilson (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - 1985--Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--January (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - 1986--Reading file/correspondence--February (Box 89, Folder 17)